[
	{
		"question": "How much bones in a human body?",
		"options": [
			"153 bones",
			"187 bones",
			"206 bones",
			"224 bones"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "How much senses do humans have?",
		"options": [
			"Four",
			"Five",
			"Six",
			"Seven"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What mineral strengthens bones?",
		"options": [
			"Calcium",
			"Potassium",
			"Iodine",
			"Sodium"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the powerhouse of the cell called?",
		"options": [
			"Mitochondria",
			"Ribosomes",
			"Vesicles",
			"Centrioles"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Where does digestions begin in our body?",
		"options": [
			"Stomach",
			"Intestines",
			"Food pipe",
			"Mouth"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which organ pumps the blood throughout the body?",
		"options": [
			"Brain",
			"Liver",
			"Heart",
			"Kidney"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Over 60% of the human body is constituted by ______.",
		"options": [
			"Air",
			"Bones",
			"Muscle",
			"Water"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which blood type is the universal donor?",
		"options": [
			"AB-",
			"AB+",
			"O+",
			"O-"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which set of muscles in the human body never rest?",
		"options": [
			"Thigh Muscles",
			"Heart Muscles",
			"Biceps",
			"Feet Muscles"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "How many chambers are there in a human heart?",
		"options": [
			"Three",
			"Four",
			"Five",
			"Six"
		],
		"answer": 1
	}
]